{
    "subject": "Fernando_Cerchio",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Lulu__1953_film_",
    "human_readable": "Fernando Cerchio created the film Lulu (1953).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8921185731887817,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by Fernando Cerchio in 1953?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8506166338920593,
            "question": "What is the title of the film created by Fernando Cerchio?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8361242413520813,
            "question": "Who created the film Lulu?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7290091514587402,
            "question": "In what year was the film Lulu made?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6565976738929749,
            "question": "What year was the film Lulu released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6540845632553101,
            "question": "Is Fernando Cerchio known for directing films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5626992583274841,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Fernando Cerchio."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5492610335350037,
            "question": "Are there other films directed by Fernando Cerchio?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5294643044471741,
            "question": "Was Lulu a successful film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36863821744918823,
            "question": "What genre is the film Lulu likely to be?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Fernando Cerchio created the film Lulu (1953).",
            "html": "yago_17341_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Lulu a successful film?",
            "html": "yago_17341_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there other films directed by Fernando Cerchio?",
            "html": "yago_17341_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a film directed by Fernando Cerchio.",
            "html": "yago_17341_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17341_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17341_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17341_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17341_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17341_122.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17341_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17341_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17341_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17341_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17341_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format for your query:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The document file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_17341/re-ranker-msmarco/119.txt mentions that Fernando Cerchio directed a movie called \"Lulu\" (1953) in Italy, and the document file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_17341/re-ranker-msmarco/111.txt confirms this by listing \"Lul\u00fa\" (1953) as one of Cerchio's films."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe information supports that Fernando Cerchio directed the film \"Lul\u00fa\" in 1953. The document mentioning 40.txt explicitly states that Rosana signs costumes for \"Lul\u00fa,\" directed by Fernando Cerchio, which further corroborates this fact."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}